Oh, that's scary.
え、怖い
It's not scary.
怖いじゃない
Are you Erica?
エリカちゃんですか?
good.
よかった
I don't know because there are so many people.
人いっぱいいるからわからない
Sorry again?
ごめんね、また?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
So, can we go?
じゃあ、行ける?
Do you always go this long?
いつもこんな時間までやっていってんの?
I already hate going to bed at 1am,
もう、午前1時で寝るのが嫌いで、
Probably like this when I sleep.
多分寝るとこんなぐらい
I'll accept it later.
遅い時間から受け入れるから
Even though it's slow, it's always bad.
遅いなのにいつも悪い
that's right.
そうです
Looks like I'll be able to evacuate.
退避取れそうだな
early.
早い
Giri.
ギリ
Oh, it's barely there.
あ、ギリなんだ
Giri.
ギリ
Okay, but I want to sleep at university.
いいな、しかしな大学で寝たいのがね
I have no experience, so I really want to try it.
経験ないから、 なんか、やっぱりやってみたいな
Is it oh fishing?
オーフィッシングかな?
This is giri.
これは、ギリ
It's okay, my spine is stuck.
大丈夫、背骨詰まってるから
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Um, is that it?
あの、あれかな?
Aren't you restless?
落ち着かないよね?
I'm restless.
落ち着かない
I wanted to ask you a lot of things, but I don't know.
いろいろ話聞きたかったけど、分かんないもんね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
My skin feels better after 5 or 10 minutes.
もうなんか、5分とか10分後に肌感になってるんだよ
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
You look like you're sweating.
汗かいてそうだね
picture?
え?
copper?
どう?
Give me a little help.
ちょっと手をかして
Ah, I'm writing.
あ、かいてる
I'm writing.
かいてる
Have we never held hands like this before?
こうやって手繋いだこともないんだっけ?
Anma.
あんま
Isn't there?
ないのか
Anma.
あんま
I see, that's not the case either.
そっか、それもないんだね
It's like a lover's connection.
恋人繋ぎみたいな
copper?
どう?
Like this.
こうやって
Is it like this?
こういうの?
Isn't there something like this?
こういうのないの?
You look cute.
可愛い顔してるね
It's strange, in the middle of the night.
不思議だな、夜中
How can I run this?
これってどうやって流せればいいの?
picture?
え?
How is it easy to get out?
どういう風に抜けやす?
this is.
これは
behind?
後ろ?
There's a button on the back, so remove it.
後ろにボタンがあるから、外して
Should I remove it?
外せばいいの?
This side.
こっち側
picture?
え?
Did I tell you to take it off?
外してって言った?
Take it off.
外して
Should I remove it myself?
自分で外す?
What should I do?
どうする?
Can I take it off?
外してもらおうかな?
Can I have you pull it out slowly?
ゆっくり抜いてもらっていい?
I'm nervous, so I'm taking it slow.
緊張してるから、ゆっくりだからね
Do you take it off your shoulders?
肩から下ろすの?
Or do you flip it from the bottom?
それとも下からめくるの?
From below...
下から...
The one who does that?
そうするやつ?
Please stand up once.
一回立ってもらって
I think it's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと、恥ずかしいと思うけど
Can I have you take off your clothes?
服脱いでもらっていい?
Congratulations, pants.
おめでとう、パンツ
I could see your panties.
パンティー見えたよ
You have beautiful skin.
綺麗な肌してるね
Well then, please take off your clothes.
じゃあ、お服、ちょっとこういうのを脱いで
Anywhere is fine.
どこでもいいよ
She's in her underwear.
下着姿だ
What about behind?
後ろは?
What's going on?
どうなってる?
Show me your back.
後ろ見せて、背中
Are you excited?
ドキドキする?
Yes, my heart is pounding.
うん、 ドキドキする
I haven't touched it through my nose yet.
まだ鼻から触ってないけど
Sit by my side.
そばに座って
It's dark today.
きょうどうくすんだね
I don't feel at ease.
落ち着かないよね
My skin hurts.
肌がだもんね
Good, nice.
いい、素敵
Put the back down.
裏を下ろして
Is it good to see it on Earth?
地球で見るのもいいかな?
fun.
楽しみ
I'm looking forward to this too.
こっちも楽しみだよ
That's it now.
今 あれだよね
When it comes to body measurements at school, they put a toning machine inside your clothes.
学校の身体測定とかって、 服の上の中に調子機入れられるで
Sho?
しょ?
So this was the first time I actually showed it to a man.
だから、 実質男の人に見せたのは 初めてってことだよね
Is that so?
そういうこと?
That's right.
だよね
Have you seen it?
見たことある?
Other than my dad.
お父さん以外に
Precious...
貴重な...
That's precious.
貴重ですよ、それ
In the olden days, this is how women used to wipe their clothes at home.
昔、超新規女の家庭的には 服装もこうやって拭ってたんだよ
In the past.
昔はね
Old doctors are delicious.
昔のお医者さんは美味しいよね
It's delicious.
美味しいと
Bottom too...
下も...
It's okay to just go with the flow.
流れでいいじゃんか
Or do you want me to touch it first?
それとも先触ってほしい?
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Will you touch my boobs first, or will I show you my bottom first?
先におっぱい触られるか、 先 に下も見せちゃうか
Which one do you prefer?
どっちがいいですか?
Both are difficult.
どっちも難しい
Are both difficult?
どっちも難しい?
I was wondering if I was going to get naked.
裸になっちゃうか、さっきね
It floats on my pants.
パンツに浮いちゃうもんね
I wish I could do it with this type.
こっちの種類でできたら
The way I took it off was embarrassing.
脱い方がなんかね、 恥ずかしかったよね
I can already tell.
もう伝わるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Will I lose my hair?
脱毛しちゃうの?
Did you shave it yourself?
自分で剃ったの?
Eh, why?
えー、なんで?
Do you care?
気にすんだ?
I care.
気にしちゃう
Is that so?
そうなの?
But since I can't hear it, I'll have to see the line clearly.
でも 聞けないからね、 線くっきり見ちゃうね
A clearly visible line.
くっきり見えてる線
It came right in front of me.
目の前に来ちゃった
You'll want to hide it.
隠したくなるでしょ
Ecchi, something.
えっち、なんか
The vertical lines are clear.
縦の線くっきりだね
He's an old man, he's looking at all kinds of pussies.
おじさんなんかさ、 いろんなマンコ見てるから、
It's the type with clear vertical lines.
縦の線くっきりタイプだね
I don't like it.
嫌だ
You've never compared them, have you?
見比べたことないでしょ
It's clear.
くっきりしてるよ
I shaved myself clean.
自分でぷっきりに剃ったね
yes.
そう
Turn around and look at that ass.
後ろ向いて、 このお尻見ちゃう
Oh, what a tiny butt.
あら、ちっちゃお尻だな
tickles?
くすぐったい?
tickles.
くすぐったい
I'm probably really embarrassed to be asked to do something like that.
多分ね、すごく恥ずかしくてさ、 そんなこと要求されても、
I never thought about it, but I sat down.
思ってもなかったけど、 座って、
Hold my legs in MG.
MGで足抱いて
yes.
そう
If you do that, you know what will happen.
そういうことしたら、どうなるか分かるよね
It's completely visible.
丸見えになっちゃってるんですよ
Fully visible.
丸見え
Can you please sit a little closer?
もう少しさ、浅めに座ってもらっていい?
But the back also hangs down, and then,
でも、後ろも垂れかかって、 そうすると、
Your legs will be burnt to the fullest, right?
足思いっきり焼けるでしょ?
Show me well and move your hands.
よく見せて、手もどかして
Have you ever looked at yourself in the mirror?
自 分って鏡で見たことある?
Isn't there?
ないの?
I've never seen it before.
見たことないんだ
Please excuse me.
失礼しますね
Open your legs a little more,
足をこう、ちょっともっと開いて、
Shall we do this?
こうしよっか
Here too, like this.
こっちも、こうして
It's here.
ここだよ
amazing.
すごい
beautiful.
きれい
I've never done anything myself.
自分、どうなにもしたことないんだよね
Really, let's see this.
ほんと、見しようじゃん、これ
Just give me a good look.
ちょっと、よく見せて
Do you know about neck toys?
首トイスって知ってる?
Neck toy?
首トイス?
i don't know?
知らない?
There are beans here, right?
このさ、 ここ、お豆さんあるでしょ?
appear?
見える?
This is what I'm wearing.
これ、かかぶってるんだよ、これ
When you turn this page over, beans will come out.
これ、めくるとさ、 お豆さん出てくるんだけど、
this.
これ
This is called Kuru Toys.
これ、 くるトイスって
This is a girl's erogenous body.
これ、女の子の性感体なんだ
It feels good here when I stimulate it.
ここ、刺激するとき、気持ちいい
You've never been stabbed yourself, have you?
自分で刺さったことないでしょ?
Didn't you look good?
格好通してもらわなかった?
At times like this, you won't know until you see it.
こういうとこさ、 見ないと分かんないからさ、
You can't wash it, right?
洗えないでしょ?
There's white scum on it.
白いカスがついてる
Isn't it embarrassing?
恥ずかしいでしょ?
hey.
ね
Things like this, once you get used to it,
こういうとこもさ、 慣れてくるとさ、
There are places like this too.
こういうとこもあるんだよ
It's beautiful.
きれいじゃん
きれいだね
It's beautiful.
きれいだよ
Is this one pretty too?
こっちもきれいかな?
beautiful.
きれい
Are you washing it?
洗ってんの?
I haven't washed it.
洗ってない
It's so hard to want to hide it, right?
隠したいくってたまんないでしょ、
this.
これ
Like this?
こんな感じ?
Thoroughly?
つくつくする?
Is it visible?
映ってる?
Should I kiss you?
キスしたほうがいい?
As for the adults, tongue dodges them,
大人の人はさ、 ベロがかわませて、
Give me a deep kiss.
ディープキスをするんだ
i don't know?
知らない?
You know, right?
知ってるでしょ?
知ってるよね?
Give me a deep kiss.
ディープキスして
Do you want me to sleep?
寝てもらう?
Even if I sleep
寝 て も
Ra?
ら う?
Do you want me to sleep?
寝てもらう?
Can I lick it?
な めたりしてもいい?
Let's get fit.
体をしよう
You licked it.
なめたね
I felt kind of hungry.
なんか、腹がした
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It's about time.
そろそろする
Would you like your hands and feet to be healed?
手足、 すやすやしてもらう?
Slowly like this,
こうゆっくりと、
Do you want me to sleep?
寝 てもらう?
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいい?
I don't know.
わかんない
My heart is pounding here.
ここは、ドキドキする
Shurikasu?
しゅりかす?
I don't know.
わかんない
Shurikasu.
しゅりかす
Can I lick this?
これ、なめてよっか
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Do you want to lick it like this?
こうなって、なめたいのか?
Lick it like this?
こうなって、なめる?
Yeah.
うん
It’s important, right?
大切だよね?
Shall we do it?
やっていこうか
Open it properly.
開いて、ちゃんと
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's beautiful, very beautiful.
きれいだよ、すごく
Try to sleep for a moment.
ちょっと、おつんばいになってみて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよね
Do you know how to sleep?
おつんばいで、わかる?
Good night.
おつんばい
The head comes out of the dust, through this butt,
頭はちりから、こっちのお尻を抜けて、
Yes, bend over and stick your butt out.
そう、 ひ じまいて、 お尻を突き出して
It has a beautiful shape.
きれいな形してる
Stick your butt out a little more.
もうちょっと、 お尻を突き出して
That's right.
そうだよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
No, leave it like this.
ダメだよ、このままだよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
I was surprised.
びっくりした
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
what happened?
どうしたの?
どう したの?
It feels weird.
変な感じ
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
From you, stick your ass out.
あなたにから、お尻を突き出して
Isn't it embarrassing?
恥ずかしいんでしょ?
Stick it out.
突き出して
Stick your butt out.
お尻を突き出して
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Did you feel relieved from the first time you came?
最初、初めて来た時から、 緊張をほぐれた?
Yeah.
うん
Shall I put my finger in it?
指を入れてみようか
He says it hurts.
痛いって言うんだよ
Make it look good.
よ く見せてね
I wonder if the men's membrane has been torn?
諸女膜っていうの、 破れちゃったのかな?
There isn't, right?
ないよね?
You don't know that, right?
その知らないよね?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
It's pulled out so much that you can tell it's wet.
すんごい抜いてるから、 ビシャビチャなのが分かる
I think I could include a crane.
鶴って入れそうなんだけど
Looks like I'm about to go in.
入っちゃいそうだよ
I might go in.
入っちゃうかも
lie?
嘘?
Now I've covered my body, body, and joints.
今、体、身、関節までいった
I might go in.
入っちゃうかもしれない
Doesn't it hurt at all?
全然痛くない?
Yeah.
うん
Well then, I'll give you some coins.
じゃあ、ちょっとコインやるよ
I got my finger in there.
指入っちゃった
Really ladies?
本当に諸女?
Yeah.
うん
I'm in, see.
入っちゃったよ、ほら
Yeah.
うん
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Yeah.
うん
amazing.
すごい
You're putting a lot of effort into it.
めっちゃ力入ってるじゃん
It's in, finger.
入っちゃったね、指
I'll do something that feels good for you.
気持ちいいことしてあげるからね
Do you know this?
これ知ってる?
Do you know anything?
何か分かる?
What is this?
何これ?
This is stimulating.
これ、刺激するんだよ
The part I mentioned earlier about kuritori.
さっきのくりとりするっていうところ
Can I do that?
していい?
Will it react?
反応するかな?
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみだな
I'll guess.
当てるよ
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
I don't know what it feels like to go.
行くって感覚分かんないよね
Let's try guessing your waist.
ちょっと腰バカ当ててみようか
What will happen?
どうなるか
I have a lot of strength in my legs.
すごい足力入ってる
Relax, relax.
リラックス、リラックス
relax.
リラックス
Right here.
ここでよ
It feels amazing.
すごい感じてるじゃん
Show me your face.
顔見せてよ
Look, look.
ほら、ほら
It's putting a lot of energy into it.
すごい力入ってる
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It feels good, right?
気持ちいいでしょ?
Want more guesses?
もっと当ててほしい?
My hips are floating all the time.
腰浮いてるよ、ずっと
Something, breathing.
何かさ、呼吸
Did it happen like this?
こうなった?
Didn't you go?
行ったんじゃないの?
Because I was able to go?
行けたから?
You went.
行ったね
It put a lot of effort into it.
すごい力入ってたね
My waist was also floating.
腰も浮いてたし
One more time, okay?
もう一回、いい?
If I hit it now, wouldn't it make me more sensitive?
今当てたら、感度敏感になってるんじゃない?
I think you're becoming very sensitive.
すごい敏感になってると思うんだよね
Hey, relax.
ほら、リラックスして
hey.
ね
Do you still want to?
まだ したい?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいの?
I'll make you moist, right?
おしっとりしてあげるでしょ?
It's putting a lot of energy into it.
すごい力入ってる
My legs.
足が
It's putting a lot of energy into it.
すごい力入ってる
Try taking care of it.
手入れてみて
What are you touching this?
何触ってるの、これ?
What is this?
何でしょう、これは?
picture?
え?
I haven't seen it yet, so I want to get a feel for what it's like.
まだ見てないから、どんなものか触りこぼしたい気持ち
Don't float.
浮かないで
wonder.
不思議
Does it feel strange?
不思議な感じ?
It's soft, isn't it, muscle?
柔らかいでしょ、筋肉
Can you see the muscles?
筋肉も分かる?
Do you understand that?
それか分かる?
this?
これ?
This is the one below.
下 のやつ、これ
Go and try them all.
全部行ってみて
Go see what you want to see.
何を見たいか行ってみて
This is still it,
これまださ、
Hasn't it gotten this big?
これ まで大きくなってない?
Ochimichi.
おちみち
When you touch it, it gets bigger and bigger.
これ触ると、どんどんどんどん大きくなってくる
It's okay, I'll have to wait until I see it to figure it out.
いいよ、見までで分かんないと
Touch the magic you cut with your other hand as well.
反対の手で切った魔法も一緒に触って
picture?
え?
Down, yes.
下、そう
Your hands are so cold.
すごい手冷たいね
It feels strange.
不思議な感じ
Does it feel strange?
不思議な感じ?
Do you want to taste it?
味する?
I don't know.
分かんない
Only here, lick it.
ここだけ、ペロペロペロって
Women's and men's pockets are eaten up.
女の人、男の人のおちみち、パクって食われるんだよ
I'll put it in my mouth.
口の中に入れちゃう
Add your hands and try the hand movements.
手を加えて、手の動きをやってみて
In your mouth.
口 の中で
It's getting better, right?
よくなってきたでしょ?
Do you understand?
分かる?
Like this?
こんな感じ?
good.
上手
good?
上手?
Is it visible?
映ってる?
Are you doing this?
こっちのことしてるでしょ?
Chichichi, you've gotten really good at it.
チチチ、すごく上手になってきたね
It's becoming rhythmic.
リズムカルになってきたね
Would you like to try it?
入れてみる?
Is it okay to not cry for the first time?
初めて泣いてないっていいの?
Well, I'd be in trouble if I said I didn't like that.
まあ、それは嫌だって言えば困るけど
Can I go with you too, Mr. Lee?
リーさんもギューっていっちゃっていい?
Looks like I'll be in soon.
入りそうだよ、すぐ
Amazing, like this.
すごい、こんな
It might be your first time if you come in right away.
すぐ入ったら初めてかも
What does it feel like?
どんな感じ?
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
pa
パ
Does it hurt?
ック 痛い?
it hurts.
痛い
It's a pack.
パ ックだね
it hurts.
痛い
I can't die anymore.
もう死ねない
Impossible?
無理?
Does this hurt?
これ痛いんだ?
hey.
ね
amazing.
すごい
I can't shake my hips.
腰振れないし
No?
ダメ?
Can't hold back?
ちょっと我慢できない?
Impossible?
無理?
Shall we climb on top?
上に乗ってみようか
Move it back and forth.
前後に動かして
Doesn't this hurt?
これ痛くない?
It's like that.
様になってる
Turn it up and down.
上下にして
It hurts a little.
ちょっと痛い
It would be painful if it happened like this.
こうやってあったら痛いんだよね
It doesn't hurt because it's hardly a piston.
ほとんどピストンになってないから痛くない
You did well.
よくしたね
I'm straddling the top.
上 またがってるよ
From myself.
自分から
Even if you stand on your feet?
足立てても?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
this.
これ
Try moving it yourself.
自分で動かしてみて
It doesn't hurt.
痛くないよね
You can adjust it yourself, right?
自分だったら調節できるでしょ?
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Are you tired?
疲れちゃった?
My legs.
足が
Shall we tidy up?
整頓しようか
It hurts when I love you.
愛しちゃったら痛いね
Mankou the stone.
石をまんこう
The stone is called mankou.
石をまんこうって言うんだよね
What do you mean?
なんていうの?
I don't know.
分かんない
interesting.
面白い
I'll take it out.
出しちゃうよ
Let it out
出しちゃ
It was.
った よ
I'm piling up content.
コンツ溜まってる
I got through it.
貫通しちゃったよ
I went inside.
チンチン入っちゃった
It's very narrow.
めっちゃ狭いね
If you look at it like this.
こうやって見ると
I can't see the hole.
穴が見えない
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
What felt best?
何が一番気持ちよかった?
I think I'll accept it all today.
今日全部受け入れそうね
What felt the best?
一番気持ちよかったのは何?
Was it when I put it in?
入れちゃった時か
What do you do before entering?
入れる前の行為が何?
Toys?
おもちゃ?
It was my first time remembering a toy.
初めてっておもちゃ覚えちゃったね
That's terrible.
やばいな
Thank you for helping me take the photo.
ありがとうね、撮影協力してくれて
good.
よかった
Congratulations.
おめでとう
It was my first time to be your partner.
初めて相手になっちゃったことに